coinbot.life 2018-04-27

# Privacy

### Privacy Policy

The policy of processing personal information (moreover – the Policy or the Privacy Policy) is developed, according to the Federal Law from 27.07.2006. № 152 “About personal information”.

This Policy determines the procedure for processing personal information and measures to ensure the security of personal information from the owner of the site http://coinbot.life (hereinafter CoinBot or Operator).

The purpose of this privacy policy is to ensure the protection of human and civil rights and freedoms when processing personal information, including protection of privacy rights, personal and family secrets.

If you do not agree with the terms of our Privacy Policy, do not use http://coinbot.life!

#### This Policy contains the following information:

– the purpose of processing personal information;

– a list of personal information, for the processing of which the consent of the subject of personal information is given;

– the name or surname, patronymic and address of the person carrying out the processing of personal data on behalf of the operator, if processing is entrusted to such person;

– a list of actions with personal information must be agreed with client, a general description of the methods used by the operator for processing personal information;

– the period during which the consent of personal information is active, as well as the method for its recall, unless otherwise provided by federal law;

– information on how you can cancel your consent to the processing of personal information.

#### The basic concepts wich used in the privacy policy are:

Personal data – any information relating to directly or indirectly, defined or determined person (subject of personal information);

Operator  – a state body, a municipal body, a legal entity or an individual, independently or jointly with other persons organizing and carrying out the processing of personal information, as well as the purposes of processing personal data, the composition of the personal data subject to processing, the actions (operations) performed with personal information;

Personal information processing – any action (operation) or a set of actions (operations) performed with using automatical tools or without using such tools with personal information, including gathering , recording, systematization, accumulation, storage, updating (updating, modification), extraction, use, transfer (distribution, provision, access), depersonalization, blocking, deletion, destruction of personal information;

#### Principles of personal information gathering:

– Processing of personal information is carried out on a legal and fair basis

– Processing of personal information is limited to the achievement of specific, pre-defined and legitimate purposes.

– It is not allowed to combine databases consisting personal data, processing of which is carried out for purposes incompatible with each other.

– Processing is subject only to personal information, which meets the purposes of their processing..

– The content and amount of processed personal information are the same with the stated processing objectives.

Your safety and privacy is important for CoinBot. Protecting your privacy is at the top of our priorities. This privacy policy explains how we gather information about our site users, what we can do with it, and what you can do to protect your privacy.

We use security measures and encryption systems to ensure that the interaction with our site is smooth and safe. All transfers are carried out using secure protocols, using the user name, password also selected and stored by you;

Keeping your password safe: you should make sure that you do not share the password with anyone and remember that CoinBot’s employees will never ask you for a password. If this happens, and someone claims to be working for CoinBot, do not give them any information – you must inform our user service right away. Choose difficult password and change it every few months. Also, do not forget to log out of the system as soon as you are finished with CoinBot sales , whenever you leave the computer after each session.

We need this information in order to manage and operate the service, prevent scam, protect our legal rights and in order to correspond to those who monitor the service provided by us. CoinBot’s Privacy Policy ensures that your personal information will not be sold, leased or will not become a subject of the transaction or will not be disclosed until the following conditions occur or in accordance with the purposes indicated above. We share information with partner companies and other persons who will process your information, or with banks and clearing companies for the purpose of delivering the products and services that you will need for sale.

If there is any suspicion of scam or violation of the rules by the user regarding the sale process, the privacy policy allows us to disclose your personal information, as necessary, also authorized by loans to persons and agencies to prevent scam. The same applies to national and international law enforcement bodies and courts, if they deem necessary information of this kind, as required by law. In addition to these exceptions, while you are engaged in sales with CoinBot, your personal information is protected from illegal use, the possibility of harm, modification or disclosure, in accordance with all reasonable measures.

#### Policy on Minors and Children.

By using this website you claim that you are over 18 years old, and also agree with any restrictions that your legislation dictates in order to participate in the sale process. If you have not reached this age and entered this site by mistake, you should immediately stop using it and quickly inform us, and we will consistent with the laws and regulations that control you and your personal information.

Regardless of the above, in order to protect children’s privacy, we never knowingly gather information from users under 13 years old, and no part of our website is formed to attract anyone who is less than 13 years old. If the website suddenly has any such information, this will be governed by the Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) and any other applicable rule under applicable law.

#### Changes to the Privacy Policy.

Privacy Policy may vary from time to time to match needs in the best possible way. The mandatory version is the latest version published on the site. In accordance with our authority, we can inform you of any changes in the materials via e-mail.

If you still have questions or need help – contact our support department
